DALIA BOLTON

daliabolton@gmail.com | (510) 926-9121 | Austin, TX 78702

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Currently pursuing the UX Design field. B.A. Social/Linguistic graduate with 2+ years experience in business development and the hospitality world. Worked with 3 different companies through internships, completed full study abroad experience, and continues to work on additional skills and projects.

WORK HISTORY

Freelance. Austin, TX

Artist | 08/2020 - Current

- Commissioned for personal art pieces, averaging ~3 per month. Created on Procreate and Adobe Illustrator.
- These works include portraits, pictures of friends, animals, etc.

Instawork. San Francisco, CA

Operations Coordinator/CSR | 10/2018 - 05/2020

- Managed over 50 customer calls per day.
- Increased user growth by 10%.
- Mastered internal systems for users, clients, and teammates.
- Established methods to critically thinking about how to make product better.

Returnity Innovations. Santa Cruz, CA Research Intern | 01/2018 - 03/2018

- Took charge of market penetration analysis of 750 potential prospects and clients to properly classify opportunity/market size and assist in business development prioritization.
- Performed marketing pursuits to include social media and professional high-resolution product photos.

SKILLS

- Illustration
- Writing
- Business development
- Customer service
- Problem Solving
- Operations
- Drawing
- Team building
- Market Analysis
- Graphic Design
- HTML/CSS/Web Design
- Visual Art Creation

EDUCATION

University Of Texas, Austin Austin, Texas Expected in 01/2021

UX Design Bootcamp: Graphic Design

University Of California - Santa Cruz Santa Cruz, CA 06/2018

Bachelor of Arts, BA: Sociology And Linguistics GPA: 3.35, Curriculum Highlights: Language/Social Theory, Statistical Methods, Linguistic Analysis, Social Analysis, Computer Science, Technical Information